# **Dennis Kontoulis**

I am a 25 year old born and raised in Windsor, ON. I'm a graduate of St Clair College's Web Development program. I love to work with people and I am looking for opportunities to expand my skill set. I am a fast learning self-starter eager to establish myself.

2970 Ruth Rd Windsor, ON, N8R 2K7 226-787-4754 denniskontoulis@gmail.com

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **A&W**, Windsor ON — Cashier

AUGUST 2016 - MARCH 2017

Handled cash and engaged with customers actively. Brought food to and from tables and customers. Kept dining room and bathrooms of store clean and organized.

# The Source, Windsor ON — Sales Associate

AUGUST 2017 - AUGUST 2019

Commision retail; handled cash on a day to day basis and actively engaged with customers. Specialized primarily in mobility sales. Gained insurmountable knowledge on the cell phone industry, as well as experience in the environment that comes with retail and sense of urgency that comes with target-based commission.

# Best Buy Canada, Windsor ON—Sales Associate

OCTOBER 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021

Big box retail; handled cash regularly. Became proficient enough to work in multiple departments; provided excellent customer service on a day-to-day basis and helped to resolve customer conflict where appropriate.

## Hiram Walker, Windsor ON — General Laborer

FEBRUARY 2021 - MAY 2021

Performed general labor for one of the largest liquor development and sales companies in North America. Cleaned the bottling floor and performed regular bottle inspections in a fast paced environment. Specialized in cleaning the heavy machinery within the bottling

#### **SKILLS**

Peak typing speed of 110wpm

Familiar with C#, Javascript, HTML and CSS, PHP, React.

Well-versed in Laravel, Angular, ASP.NET; trained in MVC frameworks by way of education.

Database building as well as database querying, specifically in SQL/MariaDB.

Strong control over the English language; thrice published via Amazon and various competitions.

## LANGUAGES

English - Fluent

Greek - Intermediate

department, such as label and packaging machines. Completed a 90 day temporary contract.

# Rogers Canada, Windsor ON—Sales

Associate/Manager on Duty

OCTOBER 2021 - OCTOBER 2023

Joined the largest Telecommunications company Canada as a Sales Associate. Made a Manager-on-Duty within a few months. Continued my career in Telecom and sales more broadly. Left in October 2023 to prioritize my education.

### **EDUCATION**

# St Clair College, Windsor ON— College Diploma

Web Development and Internet Applications JANUARY 2023 - AUGUST 2024

## AWARDS AND ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Back to back Academic Honors in first year of study at SCC;
  3.5 GPA.
- Cumulative GPA at diploma end of 3.4.
- FGC Academy Team MVP for the season of 2023-2024
- Twice published author via Amazon; achieved #1 best selling on the website at one point for a period of a week under my respective genre.